Hey.
Hmm?
Are you a first-year?
Depends. Who's asking?
This place isn't exactly a parking lot.
Maybe leave your bike somewhere else.
Shouldn't you tell me not to ride this to school?
What an odd upperclassman.
Driving motorbikes to school was against the rules.
But my buddy told me the area behind the old club building was a great place to hide one.
Leave something behind the old club building?
If what I just said rings a bell, then please step forward.
Turns out the teachers found that hiding spot by the end of my last class.
Lucky for me, I'd taken that girl's advice and parked my bike somewhere else.
Jerk! You stay away from me!
Yeah, I got it.
I wasn't a delinquent, and I definitely wasn't stupid.
But I was popular with the girls, and pressed my luck a time or two.
That one stung.
The previous girl was a little friendlier.
Anyway, since you're a free, could you lend a hand?
They aren't that heavy, but it's a lot to carry.
So, you're on the student council?
Kind of, yeah.
The stuff I do is mostly grunt work, though.
There's too many boxes for just one person.
No one even helps you out?
The rest of the council is tied up with other things.
Oh, speaking of...
Sengoku!
Hmm?
Koyanagi.
Took you long enough.
Do you realize we're in a time crunch?
Any delays on your end impede the entire council?
I'll try to be quicker.
Everything's here.
Good. Nice work.
You're free to go now.
You and your helper.
Hmm.
Is there something else?
You made a girl like a ton of boxes here.
And nice work's all you got?
Can't even spare a thank you, Mr. President.
What's your name?
And what class are you from?
The name's Kiyosuke Hori.
Class 1-9.
I'm Takeru Sengoku.
Of Class 3-1.
I advise you...
To wear your uniform correctly.
Oh, and...
Koyanagi, thank you.
Sorry for butting in like that.
Like what?
Calling out the press and making it awkward for you to be involved with the council now.
If it really does get awkward, then I'll just quit.
Seems alright.
You're...
Um...
Koyanagi.
Huh?
Right?
Yuriko Koyanagi.
Should have introduced myself sooner.
Yuriko.
Sounds nice.
Yuriko Koyanagi.
I went to a dog cafe the other day, and there was a pup that looked just like you.
They say a person's name captures who they are.
Hers definitely does.
Because she's truly as beautiful as a lily when she smiles.
After you graduate, what's next for you?
I haven't made a decision yet.
Have you, Hori?
Me?
Uh, no clue at all.
It's tough.
Say, Koyanagi, when you graduate...
And even after you graduate...
Forget it.
Hmm.
I was afraid if I held on too tight, I'd crush that flower.
Fuss up.
What's Kyosuke to you?
When I heard that he was crazy about some third year, I figured he ought to be drop-dead gorgeous.
But you're, like, not even cute.
K?
Did a single thing I just said get through to you?
Hurry up and graduate so you can get your frumpy ass away from him!
Yuriko!
Oh, hi.
Kyosuke?
I'd be downright amazed if she deserved this treatment, so back off!
This is between us girls, so you back off!
Oh, you wish!
That's enough, Kyosuke!
A man should never raise his hand against a woman.
Ever!
I mean, I know...
But women can smack each other.
If they ask for it.
She was as gentle as a flower.
Except this lily...
Had a rose's thorns.
That's when I knew I was going to make Yuriko my wife one day.
Cool story, man.
Listen, a slap from Kyoko's a sign of love.
She gets it from her mom.
I'll keep that in mind.
So, why'd she slap you?
Huh.
Why did she slap me?
Ha!
You forgot?
Happens to me, too.
Well, her wrath may come from a place of affection, but you should still proceed with caution.
Right.
Oh, my gosh.
Hmm?
What is it?
You remember?
No, but for some strange reason, my cheek just started hurting a lot more.
I didn't realize you would go past on the aftershock effect, too!
Ha!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, okay!
You're the best!
This name's strong, son!
What is it?
Ha!
If you don't know, I'd like to leave the past
It's a matter of two people
It's a matter of meaning
If you don't know, I'd like to leave the name of your name
It's a matter of bigger meaning
飲み干した、甘いサイダー
見せかえる僕を笑った
engines are always excited
笑顔なんかも いらないね
どうして、どうして
らって、曲がりいるadenness
僕を愛しいと言うの
僕は何を返して 返して 生きて 生きるんだろうが
私の想いが満ちていく
この感情の名前をそっと君に伝えるよ
生きるんだろう
マトシネ印いるそのない
マトンショナを買う
マトシネ ノ チェローヅーし
地ury切ってる
黒豆リアン等
uh gyoko honey have you developed a brother compound compound you mean complex of course
not i was just wondering if i could squeeze into sota's clothes they're probably too small
over here's you ate mochi like it was going out of style wait what are you calling me fat
because sure sounds like it no said you ate a lot of food same difference idiot well someone's cranky
if you want proof i can fit in his clothes fine by me hey grab me a shirt from your closet all right
me no i don't wanna never mind i'll get it myself is it cool if i invite your boyfriend to see sure
why the hell not it's an average evening yet so lively miyamura are you busy holding hfw here you
should come hfw what you never heard of hori fashion week well i guess tonight's is the
first one ever oh it's a play on paris fashion week you see it fits so there
isn't a hoodie like cheating they're all designed to be big and baggy
in tighter clothes you know your chest looks a bit bigger it's quite a shocking feat
shut up you suck but it's normal for a high schooler to not fit in an elementary schooler's clothes
huh will you get the door let's see him argue with this it's like a glove hey that's sota's shirt
what are you doing here you said i could invite him i did not i'm mortified must be cold with your
belly button out meaning his eyes are going straight to your pudge so what part of the cow do we get the
pudge meat from then shut up your family's always so much fun hori why am i not having any fun then
because i gained weight from eating mochi that's why girls really stress about how much they weigh huh
so why did you put on a fashion show that is the question i asked kiosuke for a shirt and it went
downhill because she got possessed by a creepy devil hand wait i think she was possessed by a deviant what
just because she asked to borrow a shirt hey sissy if you're possessed then is our house haunted now
shut up you shut up i swear when you shout like that you're the loudest one here if you want me to
stop shouting since you're here might as well plan us for dinner oh i appreciate you for letting me
responsibility for your own actions or you'll live to regret it you could even wind up in jail
let's dig in before it gets cold okay if anyone in our family is looking at doing time it's you
your life needs a do-over step but if i do it over i would still be your father
every time in every life rest assured how can i rest oh man never a dull moment at the hoodies
sota you made another mess i'm gonna clean it all up the second i get done yeah i'm sure
i'm telling the truth you always leave your messes behind i wasn't gonna this time
just what are you kiddos so angry about he leaves his messes all over the place and doesn't clean
them no she started griping at me before i even had a chance to clean my stuff she does love griping
kiosuke so you're brushing me off and taking his side then i brewed us some tea you all thirsty
listen to this listen to this listen to this um sure but why don't we have a seat first
uh lately i noticed that sota has been cleaning up really well
so he gets the benefit of the doubt if he says he was gonna clean it up later you get really angry
and it's so unfair stop it's not nice poke poke hey your daddy's on your side okay
do you mean it you're trying to teach your little bro some manners but you always jump the gun and ended
up getting so mad it's beyond short tempered so i have to wonder if you're all right sometimes bad move
i said not to upset her but you went and did it without a second thought anyway it was purely by
accident though open up sissy come on sweetheart your daddy's on your side remember there's nothing to
be upset about she's out keep your hands to yourself hands to yourself hands to yourself
where'd this hands to yourself stuff come from uh my guess it's her way of letting us know she's mad
i don't understand what's wrong seems bleak we'll have to work our way to her good side little by little
hey want some pudding i gave it up you look tense want to show it around hands to yourself but kyoko
hands to yourself oh
guess what now we're in outer space
what are you talking about we're inside do you have to be so blunt
this is outer space and we're in a spaceship and if you go outside you'll die a horrible death by
suffocating we're trying to study so no time for outer space speak for yourself i want to go to
outer space pull your notes and textbooks back out this second
if you leave this blue rug you'll die because there's no air
uh where did you even find this rug a previous space odyssey it's a spaceship and it's going to help
us build a moon villa sounds good
my big sister murdered me
address me as captain now captain cold blood maybe hang on tight because we're circling mars
oh this martian just agreed to be my best friend yay your best friends
why am i dead she hijacked the ship and instantly started replacing the crew just who is this woman
how about we let sota come back
if we do he'll grow into a weak man he'll think if he simply asks he'll get his way
he was the one who decided we'd die if we left the rug
i didn't do that the only thing i did was push him
what's that you got yourself a new ship yeah i successfully boarded one of the escape pod thingies
fueled by the sorrow of your remorseless betrayal i will set out on my quest for revenge do you even
know what that means you can do it sota that's what to think we had a spy in our midst the entire
time it's an og crew member that i'm cheering for well i suppose i'll have to turn into one
of those captains who can only put faith in herself man this is a lie
who's right i hate her vengeance
who's that bruh
practicing kanji mm-hmm lucky i wish that was my homework assignment
you're a third year in high school okay next are compound words make one using the character for
woods woodland come on honey at least let him think about it first yeah i'm home
yeah that's my smart boy if you need some help with your homework just ask you smell like cigarettes
dad that came out of nowhere you stink yosuke because of my smokes make it sound like i don't take
showers stinky a one-two punch the so in your name is hard to write huh but still it's impressive
that you're even learning kanji at your age uh we all do well let's just say the kanji for my first name
it looks hard too
so
Aw, it's so nice when you help Mommy out with the chores.
Will you do it again?
Sure!
Hey, Sota, let's finish up your homework.
What are you doing?
Didn't I tell you I was going to wash those?
Yeah, but I...
No buts!
He could have cut himself on the knives.
You're a big-top sissy!
It's dangerous for you to touch the stuff without supervision.
You always give that right away!
It's not fair!
Hey, what's wrong?
His attitude!
He was washing dishes by himself!
There are knives and stuff!
True.
Well, her wrath may come from a place of affection, but you should still proceed with caution.
Don't you think there was a better way to say that, though?
Dishes are a chore, and he's just trying to give you a hand.
He's a first-grader now.
Plus, you've washed them before.
Right, Sota?
Mm-hmm.
But you understand what your sister is saying, too, don't you?
Mm.
You see?
He gets it.
Oh!
Now you're crying?
I was just worried about him.
Oh!
Right.
It's not like what you said and did was wrong.
It's okay.
You aren't mad at me?
I-what?
Why would I be mad at you over something like this?
I promise I'm not.
Cross my heart.
I was trying to moderate, because both of you were right in your own way.
I-I don't know what to do!
What is this?
What is happening?
Uh, you having fun?
Please help me.
Man.
Looks like a nuisance summer pass.
Sorry I made you cry.
Sota's still just a kid, and I never had siblings.
I'm a novice when it comes to disciplining.
You were only trying to do what's best for him, I'm sure, because you love him so much.
I guess I was a little too harsh.
I-
Huh?
I really hate when you don't take my side, jerk.
I-I've been on your side from the start.
Uh-uh-um.
Well, good.
But, if I ever do think you're in the wrong, you can bet I'll be angry with you.
Hmm.
She smiled.
So, this anger you speak of, will you yell, don't you dare do that and smack me?
No!
No smacks, Hori!
So, this is how many things might happen.
So, it's like this.
I've seen the things I've seen.
I've seen you before.
I've seen the same thing.
I don't want to do that again.
What's mine?
They drive something to like you.
I think I can be...
That's required.
I feel like your longing Luke...
I wrote an essay in school today.
My teacher says it's great.
You hear that?
Sota's teacher really liked the essay he wrote.
Oh, my.
Aw.
So family was the topic, huh?
Excellent choice.
Can I say?
Sure.
It's called My Big Bro.
Sorry.
Truly, guys.